babyhaven.com 2010-06-20

# BabyHaven.com Privacy Policy

|  Babyhaven.com takes the privacy and security of our customers very seriously. We take all possible precautions and safety measures to make sure that each customer enjoys a safe and secure shopping experience. 

What information do we collect from you in order to process your order?

  * Your Name
  * Your Email Address
  * Your Billing Information
  * Your Shipping Information
  * Your Phone Number

How do we use this information?

We use this information to effectively process your order. Your private information is not sold or given to anyone except the shipping companies that are used to deliver your shipment. The shipping company that delivers your package will only receive your name, shipping address, and phone number. They will not receive any of your billing information. Only Babyhaven.com employees, who need to view your personal information to effectively process your order, will have access to your information. 

| 

We do not share any personal information with any outside advertisers. If you become one of our customers or sign up for future deals with us, you may receive occasional email offers from us. If you do not want to receive offers from us, you can stop them at any time by simply emailing us at [info@babyhaven.com](mailto:info@babyhaven.com) and requesting that we remove you from our mailing list. 

How do we make sure your personal information is secure?

We use industry standard Verisign SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) data encryption on all web pages that require you to input personal information. We protect each site visitor with the strongest SSL encryption available to them with up to 256-bit SSL encryption. Our SGC-enabled SSL certificate enables between 180 and 256 bit encryption all of the time. You can verify the authenticity of our SSL certificate by clicking on the Verisign logo at the bottom of any page or during checkout. Once the beginning of the address bar changes from "http" to "https" you''ll know you''ve entered a secure server. 

All Babyhaven.com policies are subject to change at any time. Babyhaven.com encourages each customer to review all of our policies before placing an order and to check periodically for any changes to any of our store policies. If you have any questions or concerns regarding any of our policies please contact us at: [info@babyhaven.com](mailto:info@babyhaven.com).
